Hi everyone, welcome to Super Serious Boy
You know all Taiwan and the whole world
Wherever there are motorcycles, there will be helmets
Did you know that the production volume is the largest in the world?
The factory with the most export sales
do you know where it is
right here
India
come to india
How can I be missing this?
What about the man who coexists with speed?
Liu Bei
you know why
Are we going to shoot this factory today?
Because this factory it is designed from
From mold making to injection all the way
Even the last painting
Everything is a one-stop factory from start to finish
world production
The largest export factory is here
first place
Basically
American brands you buy abroad
With Japanese
And Japanese ones
Basically they are all manufactured in this factory.
All are manufactured here
That's right
Raw material process
All the same
Clam
The price difference is a lot
I tell you
Many people are making safety helmets
But if you wear a safety helmet, you have to do it
The laboratory test can be passed
Able to pass EU test
Is this difficult?
And many people think that people who can make safety helmets
He can make a safe helmet
But many people even wear helmets
He can't even wear a helmet
No
What's so hard about wearing a helmet?
It's harder to wear a helmet
I tell you
(Hindi)
What you said is really true
I can't help it
How so how
Come wear a helmet
Wear it and see
Isn't that what it is?
Just break it apart like this
Like this and then stuff it in
I'm telling you I don't know how to wear a helmet
People like you just don't know how to wear a helmet
Then go to the helmet store
When you want to buy a safety helmet
tell people
Hey, do you have a more expensive helmet?
Then the clerk saw your gesture and said
You just don't know how to wear a helmet
holiday meeting
Do you know safety helmets, especially full-face safety helmets?
It has several structures to explain
So actually the episode we shot today
I suggest that the government can include
In the compulsory education of the people
Is it that important?
We start from the manufacturing of safety helmets
How to wear a safety helmet
to the end
How should you choose your helmet?
Your head is safe
This episode covers everything from manufacturing process to operation.
Film an episode for everyone to watch
So when Liu Bei, you put your two hands inside like this
When you break it apart like this
In fact, your outer shell and the Styrofoam inside you
And your whole structure
It's basically deformed
What happens when the entire structure deforms?
your shock effect
Your ability to protect your head is not that good.
Just dropped
and you know
In fact, the safety helmet will expire.
will expire
Safety helmets will expire
Nothing in this world lasts forever
There is nothing that will not go bad
besides love
(...)
So how should you wear a correct safety helmet?
First you have to show your OK gesture
pull out your little strapon
After pulling the small band open, use three fingers
hold on to your outside
At this time, break it apart
Open it and put the helmet on
Could you please help me get the hat?
Wear it like this
Button it up
That's good
That's it
When taking it off, use three fingers to hold the outside
Thumb and index finger
stretch out
Wear it like this
Because of what you do?
It will not damage the structure inside your helmet.
Then you know that neither is a hardhat?
The more expensive the better
What else would it be like?
So why are we doing this episode?
Let’s GO
First of all, when you buy a safety helmet
You need to understand first
Safety helmets come in six forms
Which six types?
Racing, long distance, compound, retro, kids, off-road
Vice versa
Off-road, kids, compound, retro, long distance, racing
Is he right?
I'm not listening
So when choosing a safety helmet
First you have to understand
what are you going to ride
Let’s choose a safety helmet
So it’s differentiated by usage
That's right
It has a different mold after each use
So this long row behind us
Walk from the mold here all the way over here
All are molds of different helmets
In addition to different helmets, it has different molds
Another biggest development cost of a safety helmet
do you know what it is
Hat type
size
In addition to the hat type, it is the size
What's the size?
very good
You fully emphasized
What I just said was wrong
So as a racing helmet
When your sizes are more diverse
The more your costs will be
Because each requires a mold
Suppose you don’t have that many molds
You only have a single cap body
Your head is very small
What should I do?
Many people will do it by inserting a sponge.
Is this good?
I'm embarrassed to say
There are some things you can't say too much
And you will also see this mold
Taiwanese mold is here
Taiwanese molds are also here
Because a lot of it comes from all over the world
Some people make the mold themselves
Then cum here
After ejaculation
Then send it to different countries
Assemble it yourself
Then you know the shell of the helmet
How was it made?
ejaculation
ㄒㄧㄚ出
What
shrimp size
How big are the shrimps?
shell shot
This helmet's ejaculation
This looks like an antenna
This is the injection port
where to inject
This looks like the shell of a safety helmet
So how do you make the shape of this helmet?
Because I talked about it today
That is to say, this factory
They are from design to mold to production
Spray to the end
All are one-stop factories
Then we will show you
How to make this mold
CNC
Next we have to get into the nature of the helmet
Do you know what the nature of a safety helmet is?
Of course he's handsome
is safe
But if you want to make a safe helmet
Then your design from the beginning
to the entire mold process
It's very important
Even where your incision is?
It is very particular
Like my classmates, I would buy one
More than 20,000 yuan of Japanese racing helmets
But it rides hard
Then it's really unnecessary
Because you know that in racing helmets
The most important part of its design
It’s the diversion behind you
And he’s riding a racing motorcycle
you know that whole person
It lies down completely
So its head-up perspective
It is actually relatively upward.
So it's a lot of action
That's when your speed reaches more than 200 km/h
When your head is bobbing
When you look at
They should turn around like this
Right, right, right
The design of your helmet
It controls your wind pressure
Let you turn when you turn
Then you feel very comfortable
You can quickly see your opponent clearly
So you see MOTO GP
You'll feel like it's not wearing its helmet properly.
But it’s not like that
But their racing helmets
design perspective
Just like an ordinary safety helmet
The perspective is different
Your classmates are basically riding strong battles
Impossible to ride 200 km/h
No wonder it gets into car accidents so often
Because it can't see the road at all
At this time we will come to visit the pier
Our factory director
Satish
Wait a minute, that's not it.
My name is Satish Dev Sandhuja
I am responsible for the operational activities within the company
i make sure
Operations within the company are efficient and cost-effective
and responsible for ensuring product quality
Delivery and compliance with regulatory standards
Now we are in the tool room
In this area we manufacture various molds
These molds are used for housing molding and lens molding
In addition we also manufacture for
Molds required for parts on various safety helmets
Everyone, you now know that we film
to all over the world
Sometimes we have to be quick
understand this
Different languages ​​and different cultures
So you see us in front
the molds they shot
Do you think this
Very familiar
Look at the very delicate back of this one
MORI's feeling
nice
DMG MORI
They are in this factory
Then directly cut the mold yourself
Then enter and then ejaculate
Except for the shell
The entire lens is also made here.
lens shot
This is how the mask shoots out
Have you ever seen this machine?
mighty button
Do you know this brand is German Wittmann Patton?
Many of the world's major manufacturers produce many toys for you to play with.
There are also many adults and children who like to play
You can stack it on top of each other
There's that little doll with a lot of stories
They were all shot using this machine
And I happened to follow
The general manager in Taiwan is quite familiar.
If I have a chance, I'll come find him and find our place
Super Serious Unlimited Channel Podcast
Come and talk to him about how he cums
He's great at cumming
Super good at ejaculation
Taiwan's best ejaculation man
Then do you know what the essence of a safety helmet is?
-handsome
-Safety
Still don't know
What about after the lens is shot?
It goes to a clean production line
After a few rounds of cleaning?
Then it will put it into a
Looks like a turbid liquid
So what about this liquid?
It's Silicone
And what about this Silicone?
If it can do two layers
Then its future impact resistance and its elasticity
will be better
In addition to the general practice of transparent lenses
You can also apply a lot of coatings on the outside of your lenses
You want gold-plated or silver ones?
Everything can be done with a stove like this
But the output at one time is very small.
This is just right for everyone to see
The complete helmet and the entire mold together
They still have some that need to be retouched or welded
All renovations are done here
We have highly skilled talents
They specialize in mold polishing, matching and assembly
We want the vice president to have more pictures
Then the vice president will put some
Things that are not usually shown to outsiders
then let's shoot
Sometimes we go to take some pictures
Factories and companies in Taiwan
People will be very taboo about taking pictures of this thing
but here
The largest safety helmet factory
fine
So the vice president is really great and important.
In the translation just now
Please try your best to translate it into something nice for the vice president
OK
But everyone knows that when you come to an Indian company
Look at this cool thing on the wall
We have to do as the Romans do when entering the country
Let the vice president introduce it to us.
What kind of god is this?
He is our God of craftsmanship and architecture
We worship Him to ensure the normal functioning of the company
indian god of tools
almost
Say goodbye quickly
Goodbye
then you know another one
The industry secret in the hard hat world is
In fact, accessories are very profitable
Mask including safety helmet
That helmet visor
There are many good ones and many bad ones.
Then when making the mold
You can probably see this too
The difference between good and bad
This is Japanese material used to make lens molds
We polished this mold many times
To ensure the clarity of the lens
But even if he is the Vice President of India
You might not believe it either
But how can we sell it to the whole world?
It can sell for more than one million a month
Then it can be sold throughout the year
More than 14 million safety helmets
The most important thing is that in their factory
One cool thing is
laboratory
High speed impact test
you think nothing
But let me tell you, the action has just been slowed down
I can't see what's going on at all
The speed of the little steel ball just shot out
According to conversion, it is probably
-216 km/h
In other words, if you ride a motorcycle behind someone
Then when the stone bounced up
Shoot it on your mask at 216 km/h
You can just wear a normal mask.
Then I got hurt and crashed.
So if today
What you have to do is to sell it all over the world
If you want to sell it to various countries
We need regulations
regulations
We asked Martin to help us explain the regulations
OK
Are you OK
So this stop is high speed lens impact testing
This means that the new European standard ECE-22-06
we will launch a
Small steel balls with speeds up to 60 m/s (216 km/h)
for testing
we will show you
What effect will it have on lenses?
If you want to play later
we can improve to
-80 m/s
-90m/s
Just 300 km/h
Do you think you will pass?
hope so
But we've never tried
Because there are many ways to make safety helmets
It actually has no rules at all
Everyone fucks
Everyone just needs plastic sheets
Can you say this?
Many people are like this
-70 m/s
252 km/h
156.6 mph
Slow down 50%
that's all
Did it shoot up there?
Yes, there are small steel balls
let's open it
This is a small steel ball
you can see
it's like a stone
Will bounce on the road
so you are completely safe
Even with 70 m/s(252 km/h)
Do you want to try 80 m/s?
certainly
They did it on this scale
How much does it take to explode?
Maybe I'll ride in front of you
I will ride up to 300 km/h
Then you'll roll up the stone and hit me
I will definitely shoot you
Did you just cum?
Cum
Finished cumming
-80m/s
288  km/h
178.9 mph
Slow down 20%
We feel a little bit of a dent
But when you feel it
it's still perfect
I think the best test is 90 m/s
The speed is about 324 km/h
Come and try it
Please increase to 90 m/s thank you
Speed ​​320 km/h
Hit Liu Bei in the face
What's the meaning
You wanted to hit me all day long over there
Did you cum?
I think we're out of ammunition
So we're going to reload.
I want to say it's almost there
So fast that I can't see it
Not even bullets
Looks much faster
You can even see the helmet move
Yes, it's shaking
No damage or fragments
So you're perfectly safe in the back
But when it hits the light and shadow, there are traces
But you don’t feel it
In fact, I can’t feel any ups and downs.
Can we make the machine faster?
Or is 90 m/s the limit of this machine?
-90 m/s is the fastest
This is already the fastest speed of this machine
But you said the regulation is 200 km/h
The regulation is 60 m/s
That’s 216 km/h
We just tested 324 km/h
So the safety factor
At least 1.5 times more
you know actually
Want to sell safety helmets in Europe or the United States?
They must meet certain certification standards
In the United States it is DOT
In Europe it is ECE 22-06
Formerly ECE 22-05
And the new ECE 22-06
there are many changes
In fact, test more often
do you want to try it
certainly
Okay, let's go
Then you know the truth
Selling safety helmets in Taiwan
Don’t you have to go through these regulations?
Because in fact, all over the world
there are many rules
But in fact, EU rules
Basically I believe it
Why
What is more powerful about the EU?
Europeans are very...
Europeans are very particular
In fact, there are stickers like this all over the world
People who have followed this EU
Of course not just one
So when you choose a helmet,
You can see this behind it
This one is sold in India
So it also passed the ISI certification
So this helmet has three certifications
Yes, it has passed three hard hat certifications
You can see clearly here
It is ECE 22-06 printed on the back
But according to the rules
It should all have
This label is on the hat buckle
-E11 numbers
Refers to the region certified in the European number
And then here are the model numbers for ECE
P stands for full-face helmet in ECE certification
This is the production number of a specific helmet
Then we have the name STELLAR-S01
It has been certified to ECE-22-06
You can scan QR core
in addition
Another very important point is the lens
It also has another number for E11
He gave you the helmet number
Only one number will be different
So actually every place
You have to confirm whether it has passed
There are three places
It’s your hat itself
then your lenses
QR Core on the hat buckle
So if you really don't know
Maybe you have never seen this brand before
But if you can get ECE from above
Then there is 22-06
Basically, everything is that standard
So how to measure this standard?
Is there a seal on it?
So it should be safe
Yeah, I'll definitely get through it
If it doesn't happen in a while, we'll go to India.
puncture test
Ready？
(slow motion)
Didn't bark
It passed without calling
Because it has a human head inside the helmet
And that head is made of metal
So if it is powered up and down
It will make this sound
Like this
It's your head being penetrated
So it will bark whenever it touches a little bit
Yes, it means it's inserted into your head.
If you want to apply DOT mark
You can just pick two spots on it
Then give you two points
Put two dots on it if the machine calls
Just didn't pass
right
But don’t think that the DOT printed on it
it just has to pass
Because DOT is actually an international standard
called self-audit
If you think there is, then there is
I think I passed
So you're in this lab
It was detected
Although it has DOT printed on it,
But when I called the machine, it still barked.
So just in case
One thing I think is cool about this factory is that
it puts them in hard hats
It tested 18 points and couldn't beat them all.
Green means passed
So DOT they have
beyond the standards of this earth
But if it writes this after today
ECE words
What it measures is different.
The specifications are another one
Because you can sell it to Europe
That’s why we can build the European Union
So is it too expensive to have ECE?
Normally
If you buy a helmet outside
Have you posted it to ECE?
In fact, the price is relatively high
Because the things you hit are different
So a high-end safety helmet like this
This is probably
More than NT$3,000
Only three thousand
vulgar cup
In fact, there are many safety helmets in the world
They are all like satellite factories
Just send it back and forth like this
They are the first
Of course, local labor is cheaper
then the second one
They have their own entire factory and laboratory.
So their entire production
Once again, I did it myself
It can really help you get it
More than three thousand yuan a cap
And also through ECE
I want to give it to many people no matter where they are in Taiwan
The person who makes the helmet
Just learn it
Or let everyone know about it
Every sign on the back of your hard hat
In fact, each of them is truly representative.
Its real meaning is
What does ECE test for a safety helmet?
Want to test this
Impact absorption test
ECE 22-06
The test is about the hard hat angry god
It simulates what would happen if you were hit by a car
Then fly up to two stories high
When you fall directly from your head
It's all about whether you burp or not.
When you see the ECE logo behind you
You can also see 05 and 06
These two things are not the same
-06 is better
-06 means that it measures more points
It is a choice among 18 points
-3 points
if it were a safe hard hat
When you were knocked down
The values ​​you read in the laboratory will be different.
Let's ask this
Master's degree from Jiaotong University
Someone who hasn't graduated yet, let me explain it to you.
I told you that my paper was handed in
What are you doing to me?
Okay, anyway
It just fell from three meters away
Then the standard here is
Its G value cannot exceed 275
Then the value we just saw is
About 150G
So the standard is met
In other words, it is below 275G
Your head is less likely to explode
This is the EU standard
EU standards
However, inside the helmet
There is another very important detail
It is usually very easy for everyone to cut corners
And it’s something that no one will find
That's it
Styrofoam
EPS
EPS is very interesting to make
It's just that it's a lot like popcorn
Like popcorn
It was originally a lot of tiny particles
Then you can use your temperature and the distance you want
and then change its density
High density EPS
at low temperatures
It will become harder
Then at the time of impact
Will affect its absorption effect
What about low density?
in excessively warm environments
it will become too soft
Then it doesn't serve its purpose
impact resistance
Then one appears
Construction of multi-density styrofoam
You can take your helmet apart
Then take out the Styrofoam inside
cut it open again
See if the sizes of the bubbles inside are different
when if is different
That's multi-density
if it were all the same
Or is there some seafood available?
Put the styrofoam thing inside
That's basically
it should be followed by
No stickers attached
No signs were placed.
So actually we all recommend safety helmets
When you reach a certain age, you have to replace it.
Because safety helmets have a shelf life
It's because of Styrofoam
But love doesn't
Love has no shelf life
Is it like the love I have with you?
Have you ever been hit by a hard hat?
I passed it by the European Union
In fact, the episode we shot today
In addition to wanting many different manufacturers to learn from
The more important factor is hope
Regardless of whether Taiwan is doing food delivery
Or are you someone who has to wear a helmet every day to commute?
Then you can know the helmet you bought
Is it safe or not?
Then you know if there was a car accident accidentally today
Or what will happen to you when you fall?
do you know
I will fly
No, that's it
Come on rock paper scissors
rock paper scissors
OK I win
how
Is this a sacrifice for art?
Money is hard to make
Huh?
It's quite resistant to dirt.
(Totally miss the point)
So when you are choosing a helmet
Those who have had ECE
Then they all have to go through a test like this
Make sure your head snaps when you crash
Will it twist your cervical vertebrae?
Then become disabled
So this is why we took pictures of this factory today.
Because when they were doing RD design earlier,
From its appearance
Then it shapes its proofing
Before they produced it?
In fact, they are based on a
The goal is to sell to the whole world
So that's why they can
Sold 14 million units a year
And then sell it all over the world
Because the essence of a safety helmet is
-handsome
-Safety
is safe
We're going to get into the color part
Water sticker
I see a lot of you
There are many colorful places on the helmet
It actually has many methods
Some people use baking paint
Some use stickers
Then what
Come again recently
That is, you will see a lot of colorful things
We will call it water sticker
But the way to make water stickers is very powerful.
It is a silk screen printing method
Print the color on it
You see a color above
It's just a screen and then it's printed out
After the final brushing
Use water with the one we posted before
thermal insulation paper
same concept
then stick it on
I tell you
The wetter this is, the better
Then what
Let’s find that hole first, right?
Find the location corresponding to that hole
How does it feel when you hold it now?
Is it like a piece of paper or is it like plastic?
It's like a thin cover
thin cover
So what else do you think is the secret to posting this?
be patient
Be handsome
Then I should be very powerful
You definitely can't
Is there any
That's it
thin layer
Then you have to ask the Indian supervisor to rate it
Can an Indian supervisor
Is it good?
sure
You can stay and work here
Finally there is the last one
Yes, still need to dry it
Then finally use a gold oil
Then paint it over
So when you touch their helmets
In fact, you touch it
You won't feel any traces of stickers
Is it because the sticker is very thin?
It can be covered from the gold oil layer
In the early days it was actually like
Some people do spray painting
Then you actually have the same color
Just masking tape
Then spray it over
Cover once and spray once
So if you want to buy one
A colorful safety helmet
In fact, the cost will be very high
Because the salary of a spray painter is tens of thousands
But this one
Three thousand yuan
Get it for three thousand yuan
Lining manufacturing
After the sticker is applied, it will be the inside of the helmet.
It's actually inside
You can see a lot of molds in the back
And what about this mold?
Follow this
The systems you see in many workshops
It's basically like a lot of the shoe industry
its tools
Or use it to cut CNC templates with a computer
I think this thing
We put some content in the member channel
To our members and friends
So welcome everyone to join our membership
You can see many hidden versions
Content that does not appear in the feature film
It’s very expensive to go out and film.
Even the machine is crying, why don’t you join?
handsome
Our third day of filming
The last stop is assembly
At this time
You can just buckle your double D
your mask
And your various accessories
And your fasteners
And then after locking them all
We can take you to the last stop
Shopping 的 Show Room
Everyone
The world's largest safety helmet factory
Finally, after going through so many complicated processes,
This is how the safety helmet is completed
So you guys hope that after this episode
You can learn how to wear your helmet
Or how to buy your helmet
Okay, this is on the wall
Since it is rare for everyone to come to Guibao Land,
Then each person chooses one
Souvenir?
souvenirs
It's rare to come to this place
The plane flies so far
So from now on you know
It doesn’t necessarily mean that the price is higher
the safer it is
Or when you are choosing a helmet
Six different types of you
How do you want to choose?
And then finally
while wearing a helmet
How do you wear it without damaging your helmet?
And when you wear it
There is another very important point
Please wear it if you come to trouble me
I have learned now
Is it like this?
OK
then like this
Then use your hands like this
right
After fastening the buckle
Does your helmet wobble?
So at this time you can use your hands
Go push up your left and right sides
If your head is shaking like this today
Or when your hands are pushing
it will shake
That's basically even the most secure helmet.
It's actually not very safe for you.
Finally, pay attention to your mask
your safety helmet
And on your buckle
Are there any relevant safety certifications?
This way your helmet will be safe
So today you should know
Even if it's called a safety helmet
It's not necessarily safe either
Even if it’s called suncake
There's no sun in it either
Even if it’s called wife cake
There won't be a wife in your cake either
So you have to look at the top of your helmet
Are there any stickers?
Then you know sun cake stickers
What does it mean?
what does it represent
Represents special offer
After choosing the helmet
We're ready to go
Walk
What if I'm free?
you can visit us
Filming unboxing videos of factories around the world
if you want to see
More of our factory videos
Or travel around the world to unbox
Various factories
Welcome to subscribe to our channel
Then here is a super serious boy
See you next week
Goodbye
No, boss
I haven't gotten in the car yet
You know actually today is a
a very sad day
Why
Because today I am the banana hat
Follow me one last time
appear on screen
What happened to the banana hat?
My banana hat turned pink
Turned pink?
Look at my banana hat
My banana hat is rotten inside
Smelly acid
This banana hat
He must have been filming with us for many years
Can't you go back and sew it up?
It turns pink. How do you sew it?
So I decided to put it
Stay in India
You didn't decide to take it
to an audience
Otherwise, just take it and sell it.
Instead of throwing everything away, why not add or subtract to make a little more?
Super serious and authentic
It contains
I sweat for several years
yes
The hat is the same as a safety helmet
Time is up
Will degrade
It degrades. It breaks down.
sentimental
Yeah
You're leaving, aren't you?
When I had a girlfriend in high school
you know the best gift
It's a helmet
Because not many people in high school have motorcycles
Wasn't that your time?
No, because I am in high school
I'm 18 years old in my second year of high school
Because in our country
Studying is a bit more difficult
Then I was in my first and second year of high school
I'm 18 years old
So there were motorcycles in high school at that time
There are probably only a dozen people in the whole school.
But even if you get to college at that time
You have a motorcycle too
precious things
Unlike a noble man like you
drive directly
So at that time you gave me a helmet
When giving safety helmets to girls
Just mean
you can follow me
sit in my back seat
Then ride a motorcycle
So my girlfriend at that time
That's how we handed it over, right?
Which one